A Guide to the Harry Flood Byrd, Sr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series IV: Miscellaneous Topics
  - F. Speeches and Statements
    - 3. Harry Flood Byrd's Public Statements and Press Releases
      - Tribute to Clair Engle, 1965 March 1 (Box Box 415)
      - Stockpiling - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1965 March 1 (Box Box 415)
      - Federal Employment and Pay - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1965 March 10 (Box Box 415)
      - On balance of payments and gold situation, 1965 March 11 (Box Box 415)
      - Statement to be held in event of death of Winston Churchill, 1965 March (Box Box 415)
      - Federal Employment, Pay and Stockpiling Joint Committee on Reduction of Non- essential Federal Expenditures, 1965 April 1 (Box Box 415)
      - On the Voting Rights Bill of 1965, 1965 April 2 (Box Box 415)
      - Statement for Record - 1965 Gold Medal Award to Edwin Cox, 1965 April 27 (Box Box 415)
      - Stockpiling - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1965 April 29 (Box Box 415)
      - Statement, by phone, to Richmond News Leader, 1965 May 14 (Box Box 415)
      - Stockpiling - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1965 May 25 (Box Box 415)
      - On H. R. 8371 - Excise Tax Repeal, 1965 June 15 (Box Box 415)
      - On the passing of Mr. Bernard M. Baruch, 1965 June 21 (Box Box 415)
      - On the so-called Medicare Bill, 1965 July 7 (Box Box 415)
      - Federal Personnel and Stockpiling - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1965 July 9 (Box Box 415)
      - On the Housing and Urban Development Bill, 1965 July 14 (Box Box 415)
      - Stockpiling - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1965 July 28 (Box Box 415)
      - Federal Employment and Pay - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1965 July 29 (Box Box 415)
      - On the Orchard Picnic, 1965 August 5 (Box Box 415)
      - On Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1965 August 9 (Box Box 415)
      - On the proposed Department for Housing and Urban Development, 1965 August 10 (Box Box 415)
      - Federal Employment and Pay - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1965 September 1 (Box Box 415)
      - On repeal of the right-to-work provision of the Taft-Hartley Act, 1965 September 6 (Box Box 415)
      - Interview with Julian Barbour of CBS on Sec. 14b of the Taft-Hartley Law, 1965 September 9 (Box Box 415)
      - On the Highway Beautification Bill, 1965 September 16 (Box Box 415)
      - Stockpile Inventories - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1965 September 30 (Box Box 415)
      - Federal Employment and Stockpiling - Joint Committee on Reduction of Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1965 October 19 (Box Box 415)
      - In support of State Democratic candidates, 1965 October 21 (Box Box 415)
      - Senator Harry F. Byrd, Sr.'s letter of resignation to Governor Harrison, 1965 November 10 (Box Box 415)
      - Re: Veto of the President of the bill providing for lower interest rates on farm loans, July 22 (Box Box 415)
      - Recorded statement of congratulations to WSVA, Harrisonburg, Va., n.d. (Box Box 415)
      - Re: Cumberland Gap National Historical Park (Box Box 415)
      - Statement to the Floyd Press - "Editorial Farm Security Admin.", n.d. (Box Box 415)
  - G. Scrapbooks
    - Small Scrapbooks
      - Small Scrapbook: 1. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1923 & 1925, re: roads, apple growing, etc. (Box Box 416)
      - Small Scrapbook: 2. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1926 February-March 13, re: inauguration as Governor, taxation, Shenandoah Park, etc. (Box Box 416)
      - Small Scrapbook: 3. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1926 March 19-November, re: gasoline prices, Monticello, etc. (Box Box 416)
      - Small Scrapbook: 4. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1927 February-May, re: efficiency, taxation, etc. (Box Box 416)
      - Small Scrapbook: 5. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1927 June-December' re: bankers, taxes, etc. (Box Box 416)
      - Small Scrapbook: 6. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1928 January-April, re: education, Brazilian guests, etc. (Box Box 416)
      - Small Scrapbook: 7. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1928 June-November, re: education, campaigns, etc. (Box Box 416)
      - Small Scrapbook: 8. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1929 January-June 4, re: Lee statue, farmers, taxes, etc. (Box Box 417)
      - Small Scrapbook: 9. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1929 June 12-October 8, re: progress in Virginia, Virginia's new state accounting, etc. (Box Box 417)
      - Small Scrapbook:10. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1929 October 14-November, re: Virginia finances, his re-election, the short ballot, etc. (Box Box 417)
      - Small Scrapbook: 11. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1930, re: state budget, fruit, etc. (Box Box 417)
      - Small Scrapbook: 12. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1931, re: roads, apples, etc. (Box Box 417)
      - Small Scrapbook: 13. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1932, re: farmers, roads, youth, etc. (Box Box 417)
      - Small Scrapbook: 14. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1933-1934, re: apples, farmers, etc. (Box Box 417)
      - Small Scrapbook: 15. Speeches of Harry Byrd, 1927-1928 & n.d., re: education, roads, etc. (Box Box 417)
    - Big Scrapbooks
      - Clippings of Richard E. Byrd, 1906-1913, re: his political career, S. 1
        Includes: ALS, 1862 June 20, Gen. R. Dodge to William Patterson.
      - Scrapbook of Richard E. Byrd, 1913-1921, chiefly re: the Industrial Council of Safety of the State of Virginia, S. 2
        Includes letters:
        TLS, 1913 January 11, W. G. McAdoo to Richard E. Byrd
        TLS, 1914 May 5, W. G. McAdoo to Richard E. Byrd
        TLS, 1914 October 17, Secretary to the President to Richard E. Byrd
        TLS, 1915 February 27, H. Ball to Richard E. Byrd
        TLS, 1917 May 2, Richard E. Byrd to [Mayors in Va.]
        TLS, 1917 May 2, Richard E. Byrd to [Newspapers in Va.]
        TLS, n.d., Richard E. Byrd to [Mayors in Va.]
        TLS, 1917 June 4, Richard E. Byrd to [Mayors in Va.]
        TLS, 1918 March 13, S. Graham to Richard E. Byrd
        TLS, 1919 June 10, Berkley D. Adams to Richard E. Byrd
        TL, 1920 May 17, [Richard E. Byrd] to A. Mitchell Palmer
        TLS, 1920 May 20, A. Mitchell Palmer to Richard E. Byrd
        TLS, 1920 May 27, [A. Mitchell Palmer] to Richard E. Byrd
        TLS, 1920 August 5, A. Mitchell Palmer to Richard E. Byrd
        TLS, 1920 August 9, Howard Figg to Richard E. Byrd
        ALS, 1921 August 27, D. J. O'Connell to Richard E. Byrd
      - Letters and pictures, 1920-1938, of Harry Byrd, S. 3
        Letters are listed in the order in which they appear in the book.
        Telegram, November 7, James A. Farley to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1933 October 4, James A. Farley to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1932 July 1, Franklin D. Roosevelt to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1933 August 2, George Peery to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1929 June 3, Nancy Astor to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1933 August 2, Clifton Woodrum to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1925 July 31, Byrd Headquarters to Harry Byrd
        Radiogram, 1929 June 1, Richard E. Byrd to Harry Byrd
        Radiogram, 1929 June 22, Richard E. Byrd to Harry Byrd
        Radiogram, 1929 May 24, Richard E. Byrd to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1936 August 14, John Stewart Bryan to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 April 22, Claude Swanson to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1933 February 4, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 1, T. M. Terry to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 1, James Wheat to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 2, A. B. Abbitt to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 August 3, Frank Hanrahan to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 August 3, Thomas Keith to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1926 November 22, Richard E. Byrd to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1935 September 27, Pleasant Reed to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1933 August 9, Carter Glass to W. W. Beverley
        TLS, 1929 April 19, M. A. Hutchinson to J. M. Weston
        TLS, 1933 December 30, E. Lee Trinkle to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 August 1, W. Albert Smoot to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 1, John Miller, Jr. to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 1, E. S. Shields to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 July 31, E. T. Krider to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1927 June 29, A. Whalen to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 February 14, Newton D. Baker to Harry Byrd
        TL (carbon), 1928 May 30, [Harry Byrd] to Claude Swanson
        TLS, 1926 December 13, Lon Sanders to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1927 December 13, E. M. Allen to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1928 February 11, Bell Perkins to Harry Byrd
        Transcript of TLS, 1920 March 23, F. D. Williams to War History Commission
        TLS, 1920 March 6, J. Sidney [Helms] to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1924 March 24, H. Wickham to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1926 December 27, Robert Hughes to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1934 December 29, R. Gray Williams to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1936 July 20, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TL (carbon), 1936 July 20, Carter Glass to John Owen
        TLS, 1934 May 31, John W. Hancock to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 7, John Thorp to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 3, C. R. Caldwell to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1928 August 1, Robert Tucker to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 7, Charles Curry to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1932 July 25, William H. Murray to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1932 October 5, Richard Russell to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1932 November 21, Walter Davenport to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1932 December 28, John Garland Pollard to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 9, J. B. Willis to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 10, William Peters to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 14, George W. Olvany to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 13, Alfred E. Smith to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 15, Angus McLean to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 17, J. C. Carpenter to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 31, Alfred E. Smith to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 August 20, R. D. Patterson to Harry Byrd
        TL (carbon), 1928 August 20, [Harry Byrd] to W. A. MacDonald
        ALS, October 26, Charles Light to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 September 4, Pat Harrison to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 September 12, Alfred E. Smith to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 November 14, Richard E. Byrd to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1928 November 19, George Browne to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 November 8, William Minor Lile to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 November 2, Pat Harrison to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1928 November 7, a group of citizens to Harry Byrd
        Radiogram, 1928 December 24, Richard E. Byrd to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, December 25, Richard E. Byrd to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 November 7, William Tuck to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1929 January 17, Dick Brophy to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 January 1, Louis Jaffe to Harry Byrd
        ALS, E. Naughton to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1928 December 26, Charles A. Lindbergh to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 January 15, O. Max Gardner to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 January 12, Angus McLean to Harry Byrd
        Transcript of TLS, 1933 February 4, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        ALS, n.d., Fred Seibel to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 May 1, P. S. du Pont to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 August 9, T. McCall Frazier to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 June 10, Nehemiah Kelly to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 May 24, Lewis Thayer to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 May 10, Luther Gulick to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1928 December 1, Alfred E. Smith to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1927 April 27, Richard E. Byrd to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1927 December 28, Claude Swanson to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929 March 7, Herbert Hoover to Harry Byrd
        TLS (carbon), 1929 June 24, William Anderson to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1936 July 10, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1930 April 29, Hilton Howell Railey to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1929, C. Douglass Buck to Harry Byrd
        Transcript of TLS, 1933 March 3, C. O'Conor Goolrick to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1933 February 8, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1934 October 24, James A. Farley to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1933 December 11, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1934 December 10, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 January 27, James A. Farley to Harry Byrd
      - Letters to Harry Byrd and clippings, 1923 August-1924 August, 1923-1924; S. 4
        Letters are listed in the order in which they appear in the book
        TLS, 1923 August 25, Ira Long to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 September 29, W. D. Cardwell to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 October 21, Charles Payne to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1923 November 6, Hunston Cary to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1923 November 7, Anna to Harry Byrd
        Telegram, 1923 November 7, H. S. Grabill to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 12, J. R. [Wallace] to Harry Byrd
        APCS, November 7, J. G. [Carlton] to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 25, Morton Goode to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 9, William Pilcher to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 8, G. F. Holsinger to Harry Byrd
        TLS, n.d., William Meade Fletcher to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 20, A. G. Lively to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 8, E. A. Hicks to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 21, A. J. Huff to Harry Byrd's representative
        APCS, n.d., Cary Langhorne to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 15, Thomas Baker to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 7, D. C. Acker to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 7, E. B. White to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 8, Lucius Gregory to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 7, R. S. [Spewell] to Harry Byrd
        ALS, n.d., E. M. Wallace to Harry Byrd
        TL, 1923 November 7, H. M. Word to Harry Byrd
        TLS,1923 November 15, J. E. Burwell to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 14, C. N. Hoover to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 7, C. M. Shannon to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 7, E. C. Mathews to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 7, S. L. Ferguson to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 7, P. D. Camp to Harry Byrd, and others
        TLS, 1923 November 27, Eugene Massie to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 8, R. Gray Williams to Harry Byrd
        ALS, n.d., James A. Frazier to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 7, John H. Crockett to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 7, A. G. Lively to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 28, A. G. Lively to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 7, Alexander Forward to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 7, E. W. Hudgins to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 7, Royston Jester, Jr. to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 12, George P. Adams to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 12, J. H. Haley to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 10, B. F. Noland to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 12, J. H. Funkhauser to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 7, Morton Goode to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 13, D. H. Barger to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 27, W. S. Irby to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 8, William F. Reyser to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 6, David Hepburn to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 9, Samuel Adams to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 15, J. M. Hooker to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 10, L. J. McCartney to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 13, Ward Swank to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 10, Edwin L. Kendig to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 7, Joseph Dupuy Eggleston to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 19, Bishop to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 8, E. V. Barley to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 22, T. W. Harrison to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 13, T. W. Harrison to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 9, J. M. Bauserman to T. W. Harrison
        TLS, 1923 November 13, C. C. Louderback to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 7, F. M. Chicester to Harry Byrd
        ALS, 1923 November 9, H. C. Allen to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 8, R. I. Roop to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 9, E. B. White to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 8, Thomas Ozlin to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 9, J. M. Beaty to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 12, H. Lester Hooker to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 8, T. L. Clark to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 8, [Thomas Johnson] to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 November 10, H. H. Burton to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 December 13, Holman Willis to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1923 December 13, S. L. Slover to Harry Byrd
      - Clippings, 1925 October-1926 January, re: Harry Byrd as Governor-elect of Virginia, 1925-1926; S. 5
      - Campaign clippings, 1925 January-July, of Harry Byrd, S. 6
        Letters included:
        TLS, 1916 January 2, E. Lee Trinkle to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1924 July 22, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1924 December 18, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1925 April 7, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
      - Clippings, 1925 February-1926 April, with scattered clippings in 1925, 1927, and 1928, re: Governor Harry Byrd, 1925-1928; S. 7
        Includes: TLS, 1926 July 20, Robert C. Bryan to Harry Byrd
      - Clippings, 1927 February-December, re: Governor Harry Byrd, S. 8
      - Clippings, 1928 January-March, re: Governor Harry Byrd, S. 9
        Includes: TLS, 1928 February 2, Thomas R. Harrison to Harry Byrd, encl. clipping
      - Clippings, 1928 April-June, re: Governor Harry Byrd, S. 10
      - Clippings, 1928 July-October, re: Governor Harry Byrd, S. 11
      - Clippings, 1928 November 1-1929 January 15, re: Governor Harry Byrd and the 1928 national election, 1928-1929; S. 12
        Includes: AL, 1928 November, [Harry Byrd] to Richmond Times Dispatch
      - Clippings, 1929 January 15-March 31, re: Governor Harry Byrd, S. 13
      - Clippings, 1929 April 1-June 14, re: Governor Harry Byrd, S. 14
        Includes: TLS, 1929 May 13, Thomas C. Cheney to Harry F. Byrd
      - Clippings, 1929 June 15-August 19, re: Governor Harry Byrd and election in Va. of 1929, S. 15
      - Clippings, 1929 August 20-October 30, re: Governor Harry Byrd and state election of 1929, S. 16
      - Clippings, 1929 October 31-1930 January 12, with a few scattered clippings from 1932, of Harry Byrd, re: election of 1929, 1929-1930; S. 17
        Includes:
        TL(carbon), 1929 October 9, Walter I. McCoy to Carter Glass
        TLS, 1929 October 10, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1930 April 24, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
      - Clippings, 1932 June-1934 December, re: Harry Byrd's entry into the Senate, 1932-1934; S. 18
        TL(carbon), 1933 February 20, Charles S. Henry to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1934 May 12, Postmaster General James G. Farley to Harry Byrd
      - Clippings, 1935 January-June 11, re: Senator Harry Byrd, S. 19
        TLS, 1935 July 26, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1935 October 2, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1935, December 27, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
      - Clippings, 1935 June 12-1936 November 30, re: Senator Harry Byrd, 1935-1936; S. 20
        TLS, 1936 April 8, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1936 September 2, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
      - Clippings, 1935 August-1945 February, of the column, Washington Merry-Go-Round, by Drew Pearson and Robert S. Allen, 1935-1945; S. 21
      - Clippings, 1937 January-1938 February, re: Senator Harry Byrd, 1937-1938; S. 22
        TLS, 1937 April 13, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1937 April 28, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1937 May 3, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1937 May 17, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 January 10, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 July 5, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 July 26, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TL (carbon), 1938 August 10, Carter Glass to John G. Wallace
      - Clippings, 1937 November-1939 April, re: Senator Harry Byrd; bills before Congress; civil servants, 1937-1939; S. 23
      - Clippings, 1938 March-1939, re: Senator Harry Byrd, 1938-1939; S. 24
        TLS, 1938 May 2, Harry W. Hultgren to Harry Byrd
        TL (carbon), 1938 May 4, Harry Byrd to Harry W. Hultgren
        TLS, 1938 May 31, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 June 27, J.W. Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 July 12, J.W. Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 July 12, Hiram W. Johnson to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 July 21, Peter Gerry to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 July 26, J.W. Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 July 28, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 August 4, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 August 7, Peter G. Gerry to Harry Byrd
        TLS, August 12, J.W. Bailey to Harry Byrd
        ALS, n.d., J.W. Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 August 13, Hiram W. Johnson to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 August 20, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 August 25, Walter George to J.W. Bailey
        TLS, 1938 September 2, J.W. Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 September 2, Hiram W. Johnson to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 September 3, J.W. Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TL (carbon), 1938 September 3, J.W. Bailey to James A. Farley
        TLS, 1938 September 23, Josiah William Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 September 27, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 September 28, Carter Glass to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 September 30, Josiah William Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TL (carbon), 1938 September 30, Josiah William Bailey to James A. Farley
        TLS, 1938 November 8, Josiah William Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TL (carbon), 1938 November 8, Josiah Wiilam Bailey to Peter Gerry
        TLS, 1938 November 17, Peter Gerry to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 November 21, Josiah William Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 November 30, Josiah William Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 December 3, Peter Gerry to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 December 9, Josiah William Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TL (carbon), 1938 December 9, Josiah William Bailey to Peter Gerry
        TLS, 1938 December 14, Josiah William Bailey to Harry Byrd
        TLS, 1938 December 22, M. S. Eccles to Harry Byrd
        TL (carbon), 1938 November 8, Josiah William Bailey to Peter Gerry
      - Clippings, 1939 January 1-October 31, re: Senator Harry Byrd, S. 25
        Letters are in the order in which they appear in the scrapbook.
        TLS, 1939 July 17, William A. Durst to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 17, Bruce to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 15, W. J. Casey to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 15, Frank Cizek to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 14, James S. Murray to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 14, Walter Coon to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 14, E. B. Moffatt to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 14, Holcombe Parkes to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 14, A. E. Duncan to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 August 5, J. H. Gordon to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 August 4, G. W. Kratz to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 31, S. P. Ruddiman to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 31, Sam Bruce to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 25, J. Lee Barrett to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 20, B. G. Hopkins to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 July 18, S. F. to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 August 25, Charles R. Hook to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 August 10, George A. Kelly to J. Hampton Baumgartner
        TLS, 1939 August 7, A.A. Drummond to J. Hampton Baumgartner